<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Services on Magekube</title>
    <link>https://www.magekube.com/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Services on Magekube</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 11:52:18 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.magekube.com/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Magento Development</title>
      <link>https://www.magekube.com/services/development/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.magekube.com/services/development/</guid>
      <description>Your storefront must be simple to use while showcasing the heart of your brand. This is not a small task. Our eCommerce experts will guide your re-platforming project from start to finish. Together, we will keep your project coordinated, effective, and profitable. Enjoy less technological overhead and higher efficiency. Update your store with the latest technology to make your goals become truth.
What you get:  Information Planning User Experience Design User Testing Development 3rd-Party Integrations Quality Assurance Responsive, Mobile-Friendly Design  You want a platform that will be a solid foundation for the next years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Magento Code Audit</title>
      <link>https://www.magekube.com/services/audit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.magekube.com/services/audit/</guid>
      <description>Is my Magento website fast enough, healthy and secure? - If you are questioning this, it is really good since you have been aware of security importance to your online store and you understand how much the site speed affects your customers.
Yet you are not tech-savvy enough to review and stay focus on your code. That time, let’s experts hands get involved and blow your headache.
Magekube provides Code Audit services to analyze your source code comprehensively so that we can identify bugs, security breaches or violations of programming rules.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Magento Support</title>
      <link>https://www.magekube.com/services/support/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.magekube.com/services/support/</guid>
      <description>Our experienced team will assist you day and night to make sure your system stays secure and just plain works. Our support plans are tailored to fit the precise needs of your business.
What you get:  Total Organization Access Focused Developer Resources Future Project Roadmap Periodically Partnership &amp;amp; Service Reviews Performance Monitoring Emergency Support Monthly Status Meetings Managed Cloud Hosting Services Security Patches Downtime Monitoring  High-powered Magento stores require regular maintenance and fine-tuning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Magento Web Optimization</title>
      <link>https://www.magekube.com/services/optimization/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.magekube.com/services/optimization/</guid>
      <description>Overall, web optimization is the process of using controlled experimentation to increase a website&amp;rsquo;s capacity to drive business goals. Simply speaking, your everyday tasks to improve customer experience, enrich product content or streamline checkout process can be viewed as web optimization. However, hereafter we will focus on the two most worthy features that you must invest to make your site pop. They are Speed and SEO. If you do not, then your competitors will.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>