<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Services on Magekube</title>
    <link>http://www.magekube.com/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Services on Magekube</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 11:52:18 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.magekube.com/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Magento Development</title>
      <link>http://www.magekube.com/services/development/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.magekube.com/services/development/</guid>
      <description>Your storefront must be easy to use while showcasing the heart of your brand. This is no small task. Our experienced eCommerce professionals will guide your replatforming project from start to finish. Together, we&amp;rsquo;ll keep your project organized, efficient, and profitable. Enjoy less technical overhead and greater efficiency. Update your store with the latest technology to make your goals become reality.
What you get:  Information Architecture User Experience Design User Testing Development Third-Party Software Integration Testing &amp;amp; Quality Assurance Responsive, Mobile-Friendly Design  You want a platform that will be a reliable foundation for the next 3-5 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Magento Code Audit</title>
      <link>http://www.magekube.com/services/audit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.magekube.com/services/audit/</guid>
      <description>Is my Magento website healthy and secure? - If you are wondering this, it is really good since you have been aware of security importance to your online stores.
Yet you are not tech-savvy enough to review your core code. That time, let’s professional hands get involved and blow your headache.
Magekube provides Code Audit services to analyze your source code comprehensively so that we can discover bugs, security breaches or violations of programming conventions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Magento Support</title>
      <link>http://www.magekube.com/services/support/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.magekube.com/services/support/</guid>
      <description>Our experienced team will support you day and night to make sure your system stays reliable and just plain works. Our support plans are tailored to fit the specific needs of your business.
What you get:  Total Team Access Focused Developer Resources Future Project Roadmap Quarterly Partnership &amp;amp; Service Reviews Performance Monitoring Emergency Support Monthly Status Meetings Managed Cloud Hosting Services Codebase Hosting and Management Automatic Security Patches Downtime Monitoring  High-powered Magento stores require regular maintenance and fine-tuning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Magento Web Optimization</title>
      <link>http://www.magekube.com/services/optimization/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.magekube.com/services/optimization/</guid>
      <description>Overall, web optimization is the process of using controlled experimentation to improve a website&amp;rsquo;s ability to drive business goals. Simply speaking, your daily tasks to improve customer experience, enrich product content or streamline checkout process can be considered as web optimization. However, hereafter we will focus on two most worthy points that you must invest to make your website pop. They are Speed and SEO. If you don&amp;rsquo;t, then your competitors will.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>